# **Adrian Lee**

### Full Stack | Blockchain Developer

**♥** Singapore, Singapore



## **SUMMARY**

Senior Full Stack | Blockchian Developer with 5+ years of well-rounded experience in web & mobile app development, object-oriented and user-centered design, and also blockchain/cryptocurrency Adaptable and transformational developer with an ability to work independently, create effective presentations, and develop opportunities that further establish organizational goals. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail......Motivated designer and developer with experience creating custom websites through JS | TS, PHP, and CSS. Strong collaboration skills and proven history of web & mobile application and blockchain development.

I am passionate about solving challenging problems that others find difficult or impossible. I always provide technical, creative, and business insights to all projects I work on.

## **TECHSTACK**

#### Libraries and Frameworks

**JavaScript Typescript React JS** Redux Node.js(Nest) Next.js **Angular** Vue.js Gatsby.js Ionic Framework SASS/LESS/SCSS **Tailwind CSS Bootstrap Material UI** Solidity Ethereum Smart Contract NFT Web3.js Ether.js DeFi

### **Database**

MySQL MongoDB PostgreSQL Firebase AWS RDS

#### **Tools**

Git Heroku AWS Npm Rest APIs Apache Nginx



## **EXPERIENCE**

## Full Stack Developer (Part time)

#### **Gohomly Inc**

04/2021 ~ 12/2021 • Remote

GoHomly is a new modern company with the goal of helping all types of real estate agents automate, modernize and fairly compete for that listing presentation. It offers a complete suite of services specifically designed to help new experienced listing agents modernize and simplify the home showing and selling process.

- Made a Content Management System to build magazine for properties
- Integrated Narrpr and other services to get the details and statistical reports for sales history
- Managed VPS server and installed CI/CD

### Blockchain Developer

#### **ThetaOne**

09/2020 ~ 03/2021

Remote

As a proven blockchain expert, I have created a blockchain-based Saas platform for securely sharing, verifying, and attesting information about finacial transactions using advanced encryption.

And also, designed and implemented payment systems that send weekly cryptocurrency rewards to thousands of active users via 10 blockchains including Ethereum, Binance Smart Chain, and Sloana.

## Full Stack Developer

#### Sucsellful

Sucsemu

02/2020 ~08/2020

Remote

Sucsellful provides the easiest way for retailers and sellers to list and sell their products on the world's largest online marketplaces with the reasonable price comparing to each other.

It helps sellers and retailers reach new customers no matter where they shop - create and manage listings, control inventory, and fulfill orders all from a single, intuitive interface that they will love using.

- Setup the DevOps with Github as VCS, Heroku as staging server, CircleCI as CI/CD framework, and AWS as production server
- Developed and launched chrome extension using ReactJS which collect product details from amazon and save them in database
- Made postgreSQL database design and created a Backend server using Nest.js framework
- Developed pixel-perfect frontend with Angular v9 cloning the design
- Taken scrum meeting every Friday with Co-founders and UX/UI designer
- Launched backend and installed reverse proxy
- Launched frontend via http server using Apache2

## Lead Software Engineer

#### **Sitebubo**

10/2018 ~ 11/2019

Remote

Sitebubo is a cloud-based website monitoring software provider. It offers features such as monitoring dashboard overviews, automated regulatory monitoring checks, regulatory health checks, uptime monitoring, security monitoring, conversation rate capturing, site speed check, SEO health checks, timely reports generation, and server monitoring. The company allows users to download its application on iOS and Android platforms.

- Lead a team of 5 front end developers, giving support to the client's multi-cultural team, providing feedback, clarifying requirements and helping with technical questions
- Kept the Project Manager and the IT Leads updated on the overall progress of the projects and managed the tasks distributed to the team
- Upgraded Ionic v3 to v4.0
- Built stable and maintainable codebases
- Installed Bitrise CI/CD framework for Ionic v4.0 project
- Setup and managed API server, monitoring server, and load balancers



## **EXPERIENCE**

### React Developer

#### **PetBacker**

12/2017 ~ 04/2018

Malaysi

PetBacker connects loving dog walkers, sitters, boarding & groomers with pet owners just like you in all major cities & can help you get a loving trusted Pet sitter who could board your dogs & cats in moments after you make a request.

- Used my extensive experience with front end and mobile development to define the structure and components for the project, making sure they are reusable
- Kept the code quality high reviewing code from other developers and suggesting improvements
- Interacted with the designer to suggest changes and to make sure the view he had about the design was translated into actual functionality

## Front-end Developer

#### **Toptal**

11/2015 ~ 12/2017



Toptal is an exclusive network of the top freelance software developers, designers, finance experts, product managers, and project managers in the world. Top companies hire Toptal freelancers for their most important projects.

- Improved operational efficiency by revamping the company's admin dashboard.
- Created a document viewer application with built-in image manipulation and text extraction using Ocrad.js.
- Developed a custom UI component to visualize active projects on the map.
- Developed interactive data-visualization UI components.
- Optimized newsletter open rate by introducing new responsive email templates.
- Translated business needs into pixel-perfect landing pages.

## **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor's degree in Computer Science National University of Singapore

2008 ~ 2013

GPA

**4.0** / 4.0

## **WHATI'MPROUDOF**

#### My Courage

To always leave my comfort zone. I'm not afraid to do whatever I need to do to achieve my goals!

#### My Competitive Effort

I can't stand to be behind of someone and like to be in front of him.

#### My Focus & Persistence

Despite any hard situation, I keep my focus on my goals and always move towards them.

#### **Keeping Good Relationship**

I like to be a right-hand man regarding all the aspects.